Fall guys
It's a party game where cheaters would win 80 percent of the time, but there once was a player
Better than even them he was called pitchy. Let me tell you about his rise and downfall
The first thing you need to know about pilchey is that he liked both tail tag a minigame created to ensure rage
And fall ball a game created to ensure hatred so he must have had a pretty messed up childhood
pichi born fall guy nine double six and the six grew up as a mario party prodigy showing
Minigame mastery and refusing to use boos to steal stars, which is something on par with war crimes
But his best friend would still do it
Even though he eventually forgave his friend a kid being taught a lesson
No one can be trusted and life's not fair must have had an effect
The second fall guys was announced he applied he showed up with the newbie wolf's head
Everyone thought he wouldn't survive the first round though as they say
Never judge a book by its cover except this time because peachy was clearly trying some advanced
navy seals tactics that he could not do only reason he qualified was because everyone else was equally stupid we were
so embarrassed by everyone the next level had to be slime climb a level designed to eliminate some of the most
Atrocious players it eliminated 70 for the final round. It really looked like pidgey was going to win his first crown on his first
Try oh no, my wolf head choked pidgey was devastated
that was the only chance he was going to get we can't just invite every person back losers make bad tv
Things could not get any worse
Then things got worse. He got a call the next day. His friend had died
Cut his own throat while doing knife tricks and painting stars
this was sad news that turned to good news dead friends make
Fantastic tv few people get a second chance when it comes to something as brutal as fall guys
And this was a totally new peachy full of confidence
Just dominating the first game then top 4 on the game that makes you realize you are the only adult playing this
Fans were horrified when his weakest game came up
tiptoe a challenge of bravery
and
Perception. Luckily. He got lucky. One of the players was clearly a savant and knew exactly where all the right tiles were
Yes a savant. That's the only explanation I can think of what?
We've solved it now leave us alone
final game
Could he pull through this time? It was a doozy and one minute and 17 seconds in pitch
He grabs the tail he still has the tail still has it. This is getting embarrassing
No one is even close to grabbing the tail
Oh, is it over? Uh congrats? I guess the crowd went wild
Well, they would have if they weren't asleep from now on there was a total peach mania peachy has done it again
He would just win and win again even became the spokesperson for ballona duke a company that builds
self-inflatable balloon fruit for game shows and military purposes
No one knew the secret to his domination
Most common belief was that he was using the camo skin which would help confuse the opponents
I asked developer immediate tonic if there was any basis for this claim, right? So we're a british company
So the game was going to be called for lads
But uh four guys has a much wider appeal and look, it's our success. Yeah me my co-workers we
Pretend it was worth it
We lie and say we would do it again
but
Every day when we see the title, it feels like our souls are deteriorating
What's the question skins? Yes more skins are coming. It didn't matter
Everything was going great pidgey was on top of the world. Nothing could go wrong
911 what's your emergency? Sorry for the late call lots of work recently
But a couple of weeks ago I saw a guy in a wolfhead hat leave his house covered in blood
Or maybe he was using a blood splatter skin hard to say in our world. Everyone had mispronounced peach's name
It's not nine double six and a six it should have been six six six four guy nine six six six
had allegedly not gotten over his friend stealing his stars in mario party and had eventually
Sacrificed him to the fall devil to become good at fall guys
This puts us in a peculiar spot because right we want to fight cheaters, right?
Like hacks or people use performance enhancing slime but sacrificing your friend to the devil
Swedish around that way of getting coaching in it
So while not banned from fall guys
He was still arrested and dropped as a spokesperson from ballona duke as they could not handle any more bad pr after that
oversized banana hit that civilian orphanage
The trial was a media circus, but pidgey had the best law firm in the world your honor
My client is an inspiration
For wolfhead users everywhere and the prosecution has no proof. He's an acquaintance of mr
fall lucifer your honor the devil is sitting in the
It's audience to jail someone for your first sacrifice
After three days, the jury had reached its decision
We need the jury find the defendant fall guy nine double six and the six
Not guilty history had happened right in front of us
He could now compete in the fall guys season 1 finale
As season 1 was drawing to a close the best players would compete in the final competition
and pitchy
Was of course the favorite
1 million kudos on the line and millions watching first game was doordash
He was patient and let other people do the dirty work. The second game was fruit memory. No peach tiles
There was nothing to confuse him as supposedly contestant grapey who recently also had legal troubles pitchy was looking
unstoppable and then the best case scenario happened fruit shoot as
Spokesperson he knew everything about inflatable fruit then an apple bounced off a wall and hit him in the face
He was knocked out. This was absolute unfair bull crap
So peachy once again turned to us here at kilian and partners we can help
Did you know that if someone pushes you off a ledge you are entitled to money pidgey was hit by an apple
That wasn't supposed to hit him and made way more than 1 million kudos
We believe every fall guy regardless of crown or headwear is equal and is allowed to sue other guys
You